[SPEAKER_01]: So welcome to this interview today.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sitting here with Natalie and we're going to have just a little interview with two questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: My name is Lars and I'm handing over to my interviewee to introduce herself.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: My name is Natalie.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm an employee at GAG and we are testing this new device.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: My first question to you is when is your next field trip?
[SPEAKER_00]: Good question, Lars.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: We are hoping for May.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, you're hoping for May.
[SPEAKER_01]: When was your last field trip?
[SPEAKER_00]: I last went in July.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, thank you very much for the interview.